export const PaymentConfig:any = {
  rifePlan: {
    categoryId: 1,
    description: 'Unlock 10,000 + Rife',
    saveAmount: 49.89,
    monthlyAmount: 9.99,
    yealyAmount: 97,
    amount: 8.08,
    monthlyProductId: import.meta.env.VITE_PRODUCT_RIFE_MONTHLY,
    yearlyProductId: import.meta.env.VITE_PRODUCT_RIFE_YEARLY,
  },
  quantumPlan: {
    categoryId: 2,
    description: 'Unlock 822 + Quantum',
    saveAmount: 127,
    monthlyAmount: 29,
    yealyAmount: 297,
    amount: 24.75,
    monthlyProductId: import.meta.env.VITE_PRODUCT_QUANTUM_MONTHLY,
    yearlyProductId: import.meta.env.VITE_PRODUCT_QUANTUM_YEARLY,
  },
  silentQuantumPlan: {
    categoryId: null,
    description: 'Unlock Silent Quantum',
    saveAmount: 51,
    monthlyAmount: 49,
    yealyAmount: 497,
    amount: 41.41,
    monthlyProductId: import.meta.env.VITE_PRODUCT_SCALAR_MONTHLY,
    yearlyProductId: import.meta.env.VITE_PRODUCT_SCALAR_YEARLY,
  },
  silentQuantumProPlan: {
    categoryId: null,
    description: 'Unlock Silent Quantum Pro',
    saveAmount: 89,
    monthlyAmount: 49,
    yealyAmount: 499,
    amount: 41.58,
    monthlyProductId: import.meta.env.VITE_PRODUCT_SCALAR_PRO_MONTHLY,
    yearlyProductId: import.meta.env.VITE_PRODUCT_SCALAR_PRO_YEARLY,
  },
  silentQuantumAdvancedPlan: {
    categoryId: null,
    description: 'Unlock Silent Quantum Advanced',
    saveAmount: 51,
    monthlyAmount: 109,
    yealyAmount: 299,
    amount: 24.75,
    monthlyProductId: import.meta.env.VITE_PRODUCT_SCALAR_ADVANCED_MONTHLY,
    yearlyProductId: import.meta.env.VITE_PRODUCT_SCALAR_ADVANCED_YEARLY,
  },
  higherQuantumPlan: {
    categoryId: 3,
    description: 'Unlock  197 + Higher Quantum',
    saveAmount: 167,
    monthlyAmount: 3000,
    yealyAmount: 3000,
    amount: 83,
    lifetimeProductId: import.meta.env.VITE_PRODUCT_HIGHER_QUANTUM_LIFETIME
  },
  advancedQuantumPlan: {
    categoryId: null,
    description: 'Unlock Advanced Quantum LifeTime',
    saveAmount: 167,
    monthlyAmount: 3000,
    yealyAmount: 3000,
    amount: 83,
    lifetimeProductId: import.meta.env.VITE_PRODUCT_HIGHER_QUANTUM_LIFETIME
  },
  innerCirclePlan: {
    categoryId: null,
    description: 'Unlock Inner Circle LifeTime',
    saveAmount: 167,
    monthlyAmount: 3000,
    yealyAmount: 3000,
    amount: 83,
    lifetimeProductId: import.meta.env.VITE_PRODUCT_HIGHER_QUANTUM_LIFETIME
  },
}

export const PaymentQuestion = [
  {
    question: 'Can I just listen to these, or do I need Qi Coils to use these frequencies?',
    answer:
      'You may listen to the frequencies without a device. However, using the frequencies with a device like the Qi Coil™ is more effective since it converts the sounds into electromagnetic waves which can better permeate through your body.',
  },
  {
    question: 'Do I need headphones?',
    answer:
      'For best practices in listening to the frequencies, both headsets or speakers are okay, but we recommend turning up your volume a little bit to help the frequency better penetrate your body (you can also listen to the frequencies at any time). Also, keep in mind that some frequencies are extremely low and not audible to the human ear but they are certainly having an effect.',
  },
  {
    question: 'How soon will I receive my order?',
    answer: 'Yes, all frequencies are tested and proven safe.',
  },
  {
    question: 'Are these frequencies safe?',
    answer:
      'For best practices in listening to the frequencies, both headsets or speakers are okay, but we recommend turning up your volume a little bit to help the frequency better penetrate your body (you can also listen to the frequencies at any time). Also, keep in mind that some frequencies are extremely low and not audible to the human ear but they are certainly having an effect.',
  },
  {
    question: 'Is sound and/or frequency therapy scientifically proven?',
    answer:
      'Yes, there are thousands of scientific studies that prove pulsed electromagnetic field therapy has many benefits to humans. For further information, please click here: https://qilifestore.com/blogs/videos-and-tutorials/fat-loss-pemf-frequency-to-reduce-pandemic-belly?_pos=9&_sid=28d9373ec&_ss=r',
  },
  {
    question: 'How Often Can I Use these frequencies?',
    answer:
      'We normally recommend that you break in for the first 7 days, and start using frequencies at medium to high volume for at least 30-60 minutes per day. For regular or normal use, keep it at medium to high volume, within 30 minutes - 3 hours per session, and at least 2 sessions per day, with a minimum 1-hour break in between. For longer use of up to 8 hours, it is advisable to keep playing the frequencies at low to medium volume.',
  },
  {
    question: 'When should I use these frequencies?',
    answer:
      'You may use it whenever you feel you need it. If you need an energy boost, need to focus, or need to relax and sleep. The Qi Coil™ app offers many different programs for different needs so you can use them to enhance your performance at work, school, home, exercise, meditation, creativity, and more!',
  },
  {
    question: 'Can I use it while I sleep?',
    answer:
      'Yes you can, but make sure to secure it properly or place it on your bedside table to avoid accidentally damaging the wires or the device itself. Also, make sure that your frequencies are playing through the Qi Coil.',
  },
  {
    question: 'Are There Any Side Effects?',
    answer:
      'Yes, some may experience a healing crisis such as headache or dizziness, most especially if it’s your first time to introduce your body to the frequencies. But no worries, if you are experiencing these symptoms, you may simply stop using the Qi coils™ for a few days before starting another session. You may also turn down the volume on your mobile device that is running the Qi Coil™ app, and usually, a day or two will be enough for your body to eliminate toxins that have been flushed out of your systems. Also, make sure to hydrate and get plenty of rest. Once your systems are tuned up over time (usually 21 days), you may experience little or no detox effects at all.',
  },
  {
    question: 'What Can I Do to Maximize the Effects of Using these frequencies?',
    answer:
      'We highly recommend that you create a more personalized frequency program depending on your goals or what you want to achieve, and use it with the Qi Coil consistently to achieve better results. You may also refer to our Frequencies User Guide for more details.',
  },
  {
    question: 'How do these frequencies work?',
    answer:
      'The Qi Coil system uses unique, powerful, harmonic sounds and sequences that are programmed in our Qi Coil app, and is designed specifically to work on a cellular level to help raise your Qi energy, attract abundance, amplify your ability to manifest your intentions, and improve your overall health and wellness.',
  },
  {
    question: 'How Do I Use Quantum frequencies?',
    answer:
      'We highly recommend that you determine what you want to focus on, create a personal program in the Qi Coil App, and start with no more than 4 different frequencies per day. Also, make sure that you drink water before and after each session to ensure that your body is well hydrated and to prevent possible healing crisis effects.',
  },
  {
    question: 'How Long Should I Use these frequencies for?',
    answer:
      'You may use the frequencies as long as you feel you need them. For example, if you need to feel more energy, use it until you feel you have the energy you need, or simply use it on a daily basis to get the daily nourishments that you need.',
  },
  {
    question: 'How will I know it’s working?',
    answer:
      'Aside from the obvious effect of achieving the goals that you intended, there are other more subtle effects that you may notice during your Qi Coil, Aura Coil, or Resonant Wand experience such as improved and positive changes in personality and feelings, lesser pain experience, etc.',
  },
  {
    question: 'How soon will I feel the effects?',
    answer:
      'It depends on how electromagnetically sensitive a person is, as some who stated that they were able to experience the effects right away, and there are others who reported to feel the effects after a few weeks (usually 21 days) of consistent use.',
  },
  {
    question: 'How long do the effects last for?',
    answer:
      'The effects may last for hours or days. We have had reports that the effects last for about 3 days even after stopping usage of the Qi coils™. If you use it for 21 days or longer, your body systems will have permanently re-calibrated. Which will make the effects last for a long period of several days even if you stop using the Qi coils™.',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the difference between Rife, Quantum, Higher Quantum and Inner Circle frequencies?',
    answer:
      'Rife Frequencies are Single Frequencies (1 Dimension), Quantum Frequencies are Multiple Frequencies (3 Dimension) and Higher Quantum & Inner Circle Frequencies are Dynamic Layers of Fields of Intention (4 Dimension)',
  },
  {
    question: 'Does it work for people who’ve never done this before?',
    answer:
      'Yes, many people who have never tried anything like the Qi Coil™ before have reported that they feel the effects immediately or over a period of 3-4 weeks.',
  },
  {
    question: 'How can I attract abundance or manifest my intentions with this?',
    answer:
      "Your mind and body have an electromagnetic field. The Qi Life Systems tune that field according to nature's harmonic frequencies. Nature is in its essence infinite and abundant. If you are in tune with nature, you will naturally transmit, receive and attract abundance. You may watch this webinar for more info: https://qilifestore.com/blogs/videos-and-tutorials/attract-abundance-webinar-replay?_pos=10&_sid=21c7fa368&_ss=r",
  },
  {
    question: 'What Is the frequency range and waveform?',
    answer:
      'Frequency Range is 0.1 Hz to 22,000 Hz. Through the Qi Life System, sine, square, or triangle waveforms are generated, delivering a clean and effective signal with zero distortion. The wave comes through as a frequency, which is then converted through the Qi Life System into an electromagnetic Gaussian field.',
  },
  {
    question: 'What Can I Do If I’m Not Satisfied with the Product?',
    answer:
      'We are so confident that our Qi Coil will transform your life that we are willing to offer you a 30 day Satisfaction Guarantee.',
  },
  {
    question: 'Do you offer Financing?',
    answer:
      'We are committed to everyone having the opportunity to experience our devices so we thought of ways to make the cost one less thing to worry about.' +
      "As a person living in the US, the best course of action is to take our financing partner, Klarna as your financing option. It's really easy to apply, just select 'Order now, Pay Later with Klarna' as the payment option on the checkout page before completing your order. Then, wait for the prompts to enter your personal information." +
      'We also have an in-house financing option. To start this process, please confirm which device or system are you interested in getting, and let us know when you are available for one of our representatives to call you to help you with your financing process.',
  },
];